Now, look, I know that I went through that very fast, but maybe, uh, you're still, uh, blinking
제가 아주 빨리 지나갔다는 건 알지만 어쩌면 당신은 아직도 눈을 깜빡이고 있을지도
at the end of that.
몰라요
But that's because the point is that you should go back now and do this yourself and see it.
하지만 중요한 건 지금 돌아가서 직접 봐야 한다는 거예요
And as you run that code and you see what's going on in the modal screens, I think it's going to make
코드를 실행하고 모드 스크린에서 무슨 일이 벌어지는지 보면 완전히
complete sense.
이해가 될 거예요
Um, in case you have any problems with that, uh, hugging face token, I'm going to put better instructions
포옹하는 얼굴 토큰에 문제가 생길 수도 있으니 Jupyter 연구소에 더 나은 방법을
in the Jupyter lab.
알려줄게요
So that's very clear for you.
아주 명확하죠
And yeah, if I think you'll find that it will, that it will be fairly straightforward and you'll see
네, 그렇게 될 것 같다면 꽤 간단할 겁니다 어떻게 작동하는지 왜 그렇게
how that works and why it's working so fast.
빠른지 보실 거예요
There's the first time you run it for a while.
처음으로 실행하는 거죠
There's several minutes for it to warm up.
예열하려면 몇 분 걸려요
But then subsequently, because we've cached the model weights and we've loaded it into memory, it
하지만 그 후에 모델 무게를 캐시에 넣고 메모리에 로드했기 때문에
should run quickly as it did just then.
방금처럼 빨리 실행될 거예요
So with that, you have now learned how to take a model and how to deploy it to production so that people
이제 모델을 가져다가 프로덕션에 배포하는 법을 배웠습니다 주피터 랩 같은
could call it just with Python code for production purposes within applications outside something like
것의 외부의 응용 프로그램에서 프로덕션 목적으로 파이썬 코드로 호출할 수 있도록요
And hopefully you're now beginning to appreciate that.
여러분도 이제 그걸 느끼기 시작하셨길 바라요
We do have a big week, and it is an epic project, and there's a lot to be done.
이번 주는 중요한 한 주예요 에픽 프로젝트로 할 일이 많죠
In fact, uh, the next day's worth of activities is the biggest of the lot.
사실 다음 날 할 활동이 가장 큰 활동이에요
There's an awful lot happening.
많은 일이 벌어지고 있어요
Um, but just to remind yourself for today that that this was about deploying models in production using
하지만 오늘 여러분께 상기시켜 드리자면 이건 서버리스 비 플랫폼 모듈을 이용한 프로덕션의
modal, the serverless platform.
모델 배포에 관한 거였어요
In some ways, it's similar to when we deployed a model or I deployed a model to the hugging face using
어떤 면에서는 모델을 배포하거나 얼굴 엔드포인트를 이용해 안는 얼굴에 모델을 배포할
hugging face endpoints.
때와 비슷해요
Um, but you can see the the extra functionality that you get with this, the ability to configure infrastructure
하지만 이것으로 얻는 추가 기능성 코드로 인프라를 구성하는
with code and the way that the pricing works, it's a very, very powerful platform.
기능 가격 책정 방식 아주 아주 강력한 플랫폼이죠
Next time you'll be able to build an advanced Wragg solution, you're saying I already you already got
다음에는 고급 Wragg 솔루션을 만들 수 있을 거예요 이미 Wragg를 갖고 있다고요?
Wragg.
래그, 끝났어요
We know Wragg well.
래그를 잘 알죠
You're going to know it even more.
더 잘 알게 될 거예요
Next time.
다음에요
We're going to use Wragg.
래그를 쓸 거예요
We're going to do it directly without chain.
체인 없이 바로 할 거예요
We're pros now.
우린 이제 프로예요
We don't need long chain.
긴 체인은 필요 없어요
We can do it ourselves.
우리가 하면 돼요
We're going to look things up in a Chrome data store and use it to give context to a model, but it's
크롬 데이터 스토어에서 찾아보고 모델에 컨텍스트를 주는 데 사용할 거예요
going to be an enormous great data store.
아주 방대한 데이터 스토어가 되겠죠
And we're going to build something called an ensemble model, which is a kind of model that combines
앙상블 모델이라는 걸 만들 거예요 여러 모델을
the best of multiple models.
합친 모델이죠
And we're going to be able to deliver production ready code that will span multiple models.
다양한 모델을 포괄하는 생산 준비 코드를 제공할 수 있죠
So it's going to be about, uh, really strengthening your skill set, building expertise as you make
여러분의 기술을 강화하고 전문성을 구축하는 게 중요합니다 LM 엔지니어링에
the transition from being a knowledgeable in LM engineering to being a master of LM engineering.
관해 아는 것에서 LM 엔지니어링의 달인이 되는 과정에서요
And with that, I'll see you next time.
그럼 다음 시간에 뵙죠